Guide to the Alton Abraham Collection of Sun Ra 1822-2008
University of Chicago Library
- Series VI: Business Records
  - Notebook, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - General correspondence, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Financial records, legal records and correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Enterplanetary Koncepts, registrations, licenses and notes, 1970- 1973 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - European travel, financial records, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Film equipment and production, promotional material, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - General correspondence, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - General correspondence, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Notebook, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Checkbook, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - American Federation of Musicians, correspondence, 1971-1975 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - General correspondence, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 5-6)
  - Legal correspondence and agreements, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Poetry of America, correspondence, circa 1972 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - General correspondence, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - General correspondence, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Travel insurance policies, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Down Beat magazine, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Triangle Guide magazine, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Copyright manual and forms, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Notebook, circa 1973 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Mailing book, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Movie Maker magazine, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - General correspondence, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 9-10)
  - Dimpna B. Clarin, program, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - General correspondence, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Student Activities Programming, magazine, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 3-4)
  - General correspondence, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 5-6)
  - Notebook, 1976-1979 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Notebook, 1976-1980 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - General correspondence, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - General correspondence, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Judith A. Holten, "The Endangered Species: A One Act History Play for Children," script, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Record orders, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Jefferson 42, magazine, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - General correspondence, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 5-6)
  - Jazz Echo, newsletter, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Jazz Forum, magazine, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Navy Pier performance contract, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - General correspondence, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 10-11)
  - El Saturn Research, "Hot Hits Fresh from the Sun..." broadside, circa 1970s (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Saturn Records Research, announcement, circa 1970s (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Symac Productions, Johnnie Walker announcement, circa 1970s (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Recording agreements, circa 1970s (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Financial records, circa 1970s (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Keystone Printed Specialties Co., Inc., product samples, circa 1970s (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Notes, circa 1970s (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Notebooks, circa 1970s (Box 27, Folder 4-5)
  - Legal forms, circa 1970s (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Financial records, circa 1970s (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Farfisa electric organ, instruction manual, circa 1970s (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Audio recording equipment, promotional material, circa 1970s (Box 27, Folder 9-10)
  - Saturn Records Research, catalog of Sun Ra albums, circa 1970s- 1980s (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Notebook, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - John Gilmore, correspondence, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Otis Rush, European tour itinerary, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - General correspondence, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Notebook, 1980-1982 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Notebook, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Pierre Fablet, correspondence, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - General correspondence, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - General correspondence, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - General correspondence, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Dimpna B. Clarin, broadsides, 1983-1985 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - General correspondence, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Ed Michel, correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Down Beat magazine, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - General correspondence, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - General correspondence, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Enterplanetary Koncepts, contract with Guthrie Theater, Minneapolis, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - General correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - International Jazz Federation, membership application and magazine, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Notebooks, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - General correspondence, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Mitchell W. Boisseau, resume, photograph and clippings, circa 1980s (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - El Saturn Research, Sun Ra recordings broadside, circa 1980s (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Notebooks, circa 1980s (Box 29, Folder 9-15)
  - Notebooks, circa 1980s (Box 30, Folder 1-2)
  - Financial records, 1980s-1990s (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Jazz museums and parks, publications and reports, 1980s-1990s (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Enterplanetary Koncepts, draft agreement, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Notes, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Legal forms, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Audio recording, promotional material and notes, circa 1980s- 1990s (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - "Pat Patrick: Saxophonist, Musicologist, Composer," brochure, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - General correspondence, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Royalties and licensing, correspondence and notes, 1990-1994 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - General correspondence, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - John Szwed, correspondence, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - General correspondence, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - General correspondence, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - General correspondence, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 2-4)
  - David Henderson, correspondence, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Notes, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - General correspondence, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - General correspondence, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Hartmut Geerken, correspondence, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - David DeShong, correspondence, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - General correspondence, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Evidence Music, royalty statement, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - General correspondence, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Trademark bulletin and application, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - General correspondence, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - General correspondence, circa 1990s (Box 32, Folder 5-6)
  - Independent music promotion, pamphlets, circa 1990s (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - El Saturn Research, letterhead, circa 1990s (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Ihnfinity Research Inc., letterhead, circa 1990s (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Saturn Research, letterhead, circa 1990s (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - General correspondence, undated (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Notes, undated (Box 32, Folder 12-13)
  - Legal forms, undated (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - El Saturn Records, recording agreement forms, undated (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - LP center labels, order forms, undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Allied Record Distributing Company, agreement forms, undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Legal agreement mimeograph stencil, undated (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - El Saturn Research, invoice forms, undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - El Saturn Research, Alton Abraham business cards, undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Thmei Research, letterhead, undated (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Ihnfinity Research Inc., letterhead, undated (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - El Saturn Research, letterhead, undated (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Atra Productions, letterhead, undated (Box 33, Folder 10-11)
  - Saturn Records Research and Saturn "II" Research, letterhead, undated (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Series VII: Alton Abraham
  This series documents Alton Abraham's education, employment, personal life, and outside interests. There is also some material related to Abraham's friends, associates and family members. This series is organized into six subseries.
  Subseries 1: Spirituality and the Supernatural, contains books, periodicals and print ephemera reflecting Alton Abraham's interest in subjects such as religion, Egyptology, the occult, alternative medicine, extraterrestrials, and the afterlife. These materials span the years 1822-1988. This subseries is organized by format: There is a section of hardcover books; a section of paperback books; a section of periodicals; and a section of print ephemera. Each section is further organized alphabetically by author or organization.
  Subseries 2: Science and Technology, contains material related to Abraham's lifelong interest in these subjects, as well as records of his education and employment in technical fields. Abraham collected material on a multitude of topics, such as nutrition, chemistry, psychology, communications technology, electronic surveillance, photography, agriculture, aerospace, and many more. Included are publications, printed ephemera, technical specifications, correspondence and notes. Files are organized chronologically from the 1920s-1993; undated materials are included at the end of the subseries.
  Subseries 3: Politics and Society, contains publications and print ephemera on topics such as black nationalism, radical leftism, African society, and minority social issues. Files are organized chronologically from 1962-1992, with undated materials at the end of the subseries.
  Subseries 4: Music Instruction, contains of Alton Abraham's collection of sheet music, songbooks, and instruction books. Files are arranged chronologically from 1923-1982, though most of the subseries consists of instruction books for popular music of the 1960s-1970s.
  Subseries 5: Knights of Music, is a small collection of material documenting this African-American men's choral group, to which Alton Abraham belonged in the early 1950s. This subseries contains some of the group's concert programs and business records, as well as Abraham's certificate of membership and collection of choral music songbooks. This subseries also contains some related material that documents other unique aspects of African-American culture in mid-20th century Chicago: An invitation to the 1950 "Queen of May" frolic hosted by the Sepians, and an elaborate program for a performance of the Mildred B. Haessler Ballet Group. Material in this subseries dates from 1887-1953, but is concentrated in the early 1950s.
  Subseries 6: Entrepreneurship, consists of correspondence, publications and printed ephemera dating from the 1960s-1980s. The majority of this material is direct marketing correspondence promoting pyramid capital schemes and other spurious business opportunities. Also included are correspondence and publications from the Bureau of Land Management, catalogs and correspondence from manufacturing concerns, and typescript excerpts of J.D. Borthwick's Three Years in California.
  Subseries 7: Correspondence, Notes and Ephemera, contains material collected by Alton Abraham and his friends and family. Included are materials related to travel, book collecting, automobiles, employment, education, and civic affairs. This subseries also contains several files of notes and correspondence on a variety of personal subjects. Files are organized chronologically from 1929-1978, with undated material at the end of the subseries.
  Oversize publications, clippings, sheet music and ephemera have been transferred to Series X: Subseries 6; among these items are several large-format posters and radical publications. Artifactual objects, such as decorative ornaments and other personal items, are in Series IX. Restricted materials, consisting of personal financial records, academic records, medical records, and identification and registration documents, have been transferred to Series XII.
  - Subseries 1: Spirituality and the Supernatural
    - Avalon, Arthur, Hymn to Kāli Karpūrādi-Stotra, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Belzoni, G., Narrative of the Operations and Recent Discoveries in Egypt and Nubia, Vol. II, 1822 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Besant, Annie, Thought Power: Its Control and Culture, 1953 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Blavatsky, H.P., The Key to Theosophy, 1889 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Burroughs, Joseph Birkbeck, Titan, Son of Saturn, 1921 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Curtiss, Harriette Augusta and F. Homer Curtiss, The Voice of Isis, 1935 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - DeClaremont, Lewis, The Ancient's Book of Magic, undated (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Francis, J.R., The Encyclopedia of Death and Life in the Spirit- World, 1900 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Haddock, Frank Channing, The Personal Atmosphere, 1908 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Hall, Trowbridge, Egypt in Silhouette, 1928 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Irving, Washington, Mahomet and his Successors, 1849 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Jiharājadāsa, C., H.P.B. Speaks, Vol. I, 1950 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Jiharājadāsa, C., H.P.B. Speaks, Vol. II, 1951 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Meyer, Rev. Fulgence, The Seraphic Highway, 1925 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Parsons, Albert Ross, New Light from the Great Pyramid, 1893 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Priestley, Richard, Nimrod: A Discourse on Certain Passages of History and Fable, Vol. I, 1828 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Priestley, Richard, Nimrod: A Discourse on Certain Passages of History and Fable, Vol. III, 1828 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Priestley, Richard, Nimrod: A Discourse on Certain Passages of History and Fable, Vol. IV, 1829 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Proctor, Richard A., Other Worlds than Ours, 1902 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Reed, Lucas A., Astronomy and the Bible, 1919 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Speer, Robert E., Race and Race Relations, 1924 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Spivey, Thomas Sawyer, Lavius Egyptus, 1904 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Stockham, Alice B., Tokology: A Book for Every Woman, 1889 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Unwin, T. Fisher, The Mystics, Ascetics, and Saints of India, 1905 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Volney, C.F., The Ruins, 1920 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Watchtower Bible and Tract Society, You May Survive Armageddon into God's New World, 1955 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Wood, Ernest, Concentration, 1949 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Woodroffe, Sir John, The World as Power, Power as Matter, 1923 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Unidentified author, Supernatural Religion: An Inquiry into the Reality of Divine Revelation, Vol. II, 1874 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Besant, Annie, Theosophy and Christianity, 1941 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Boots, Gypsy and Thorwald Bosie, Turn On-Turn Off, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Cayce, Edgar E., Atlantis: Fact or Fiction?, 1962 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Copen, Bruce, How Radiesthesia Can Help You, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Fox, Emmet, Find and Use Your Inner Power, undated (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Heline, Corinne, Healing and Regeneration through Color, 1943 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Heline, Corinne, Healing and Regeneration through Music, 1943 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - McCain, Betty, Abortion and Karma, 1960 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - McDonald, John, The Magic Story: The Message of a Master, 1952 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Moser, Robert E., Mental and Astral Projection, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Namikoshi, Tokujiro, Japanese Finger-Pressure Therapy, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Platoff, Raphael P., The Light for Tomorrow: H3, undated (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Quinn, Pete, Policy Pete's Dream Book, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Raleigh, Dr. A.S., The Hermetic Art: An Introduction to the Art of Alchemy, 1919 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Rogers, J.A., 100 Amazing Facts About the Negro (with complete proof), 1957 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Rogers, L.W., The Forces We Generate, 1924 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Rogers, L.W., Gods in the Making, 1925 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Rogers, L.W., The Purpose of Life, 1945 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Rogers, L.W., Soul Powers and Possibilities, 1925 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Rogers, L.W., Self Development and Power, 1910 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Saxmann, Robert Beatty, Rebirth, Transmigration and Reincarnation, 1937 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Scharder, Dr. M.F., Sacred Wisdom of the Ancients!, 1959 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Shay, Joseph M., Out of Body Consciousness, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Urides, Eros (a Martian), The Planet Mars and its Inhabitants, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Whitman, Edward, The Books of the Planets: the Book of Saturn, undated (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Woodland, Samuel Francis, All That's Love-ly, 1907 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Unidentified Author, Ancient History, undated (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Unidentified Author, I am Decrees, 1937 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Holy Bible (King James Version), 1964 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Beyond Reality, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - The Cosmic Dawn, 1930 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Cosmic Voice, Vol. I, 1955-61 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Fate and Fortune, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Flying Saucers, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Man, Myth, and Magic, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Occult Digest, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - The Occult Press Review, 1923 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Psychic, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Psychic Dimensions, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Science of Mind, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - The Truth Seeker, 1955-1956 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Abraham, Adam A., 1983 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Aetherius Society, 1961 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - American Cosmic-Solar Research Center, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - American Federation of Young Theosophists, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Ansaru Allah Community, undated (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Ascended Master's Darjeeling Council of God's Will, 1966-1975 (Box 45, Folder 6-7)
    - The Association for Research and Enlightenment, undated (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Astara Foundation, 1966-1968 (Box 45, Folder 9-11)
    - Astrology, undated (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Biosophical Society, 1956 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - The Bridge to Freedom, undated (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - The Brotherhood of Light, 1934 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - The Children of God, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - The Christian Community, undated (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - The Christian Vernacular Education Society, 1890 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Church of Illumination, undated (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - E.S.P. Laboratory, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - The Great White Brotherhood, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 4-5)
    - The Holy House of Ra, undated (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - International Imports, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - The Mayans, 1936-64 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - The New Age Truth Organization, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Nubian Islaamic Hebrews, undated (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Osiris Book Service Ltd., undated (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - The Philosophical Research Society, 1987-1988 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Pyramids, 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Rogers, J.A., 1960 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Society of Transcendent Science, 1923 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Stewart, Kilton, undated (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Watchtower Bible and Tract Society of New York, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Watchtower Bible and Tract Society of Pennsylvania, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - von Winterstein, Alfred Frh., undated (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Unidentified authors, "The Evil Eye" undated "Everyman's History of the Jews," undated "Indexed Synopsis," undated "The Law of Attraction and the Science of Self-Knowledge," undated "The Number of the Beast," undated "The Seven Portals," undated "Topical Helps to the American Standard Bible," 1911 "The Truth about Jesus," undated (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Subseries 2: Science and Technology
    - Battle Creek Food Company, "Healthful Living," pamphlet, circa 1920s (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - United States War Department, Detector Set AN/PRS-1, manual, 1944 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - American Institute of Engineering and Technology, Drafting: The Language of Industry, volume 2, textbook, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Chicago City Junior College, An Introduction to College Chemistry in the Laboratory, textbook, circa 1949 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Chemistry course, lecture notes, 1949 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Psychology course, lecture notes and examination, 1949 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - X-ray technical instruction, lecture notes, syllabus and readings, 1950-1959 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - X-ray equipment, manuals, circa 1950-1959 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Milton S. Kiser, Analyzing and Tracing TV Circuits, manual, 1954 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Edmund Scientific Company, Infra-Red Light and Its Uses, manual, circa 1954 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Boy Scouts of America, catalog, 1956 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Laboratory equipment and supplies, catalogs, circa 1950s-1970 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - American Society of X-Ray Technicians, newsletter, 1960 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Mössbauer spectroscopy, conference proceedings, technical specifications and reprint, 1963-1967 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Technical sketches, 1964 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Electronic Technician, magazine, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Lance Antenna Corporation, brochure, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - PF Reporter, magazines, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 2-3)
    - Professional Photographers of America, Professional Photographers Product Guide, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Radio Electronics, magazine, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Science and Mechanics, magazine, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Nova-Tech aviation equipment, correspondence, circa 1966 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Surveillance and security equipment, correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Hydrogen generator, operating instructions, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Motorola Semiconductor Products, manuals and catalog, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - New York University, Summer Workshop in Television and Radio, bulletin, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Metal detectors, correspondence, circa 1967 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Agricultural Extension Service, University of California, "Selected Publications on Growing Plants Without Soil," bibliography, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Indiana Botanic Gardens, Inc., catalog, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Joseph D. Cooper, Nikon F Nikkormat Pocket Companion, manual, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Bruce Copen, The Radionic Computer Handbook, 1969-1974 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - NSEC, cryogenic accessories, specifications, circa 1960s (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Pyrotechnics operating instructions, circa 1960s (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Space Travel: A Golden Stamp Book, circa 1960s (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Telephone equipment, catalog and clipping, circa 1960s (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Metalworking supplies and equipment, catalogs, circa 1960s-1976 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Model Rocketry, magazine, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Olivetti Logos 27-1 calculator, specifications, circa 1970 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Occidental Institute of Chinese Studies, acupuncture, correspondence, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Nutrition and diet, correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Science and Mechanics, magazine, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Scott R. French, The Big Brother Game, monograph, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Surveillance equipment, brochures and correspondence, circa 1975 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Rapid Electroplating Process, Inc., correspondence, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Newsweek, magazine, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Holography, correspondence, circa 1979-1980 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Photograph equipment catalogs, circa 1970s (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Panasonic Satellite Products, catalog, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Gero Vita International, brochure, circa 1987 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Chicago Academy of Sciences, "Science and Art: Creativity and Motivation," conference program and correspondence, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Electronics courses, correspondence, undated (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - IBM Field Engineering Education, Selectric I/O Printer, guide, undated (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Castolite Company, correspondence, undated (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Medical procedures, notes, undated (Box 49, Folder 20)